moderating of
the 15
minute of
the 15 m 30
[Music]
m 1
hour shift of
structure to
continue with the higher to continue
s with the higher
ATT all right does this make any sense
is it clear is it not what I've been
saying for two weeks but now it's simple
because it literally tells you like it's
everything I've been saying for two
weeks but now it's just a step like you
got to do it like there there's levels
to this [\h__\h] so now this is the next
level so now that we have a higher low
what do we have to do we are starting to
create
after
we are starting to create a potential
higher low lower high we are in constant
moderation of 15 minute 30 minute 1 hour
shift of structure to continue with the
higher time
frame which time frame
frame is the correct one you may
ask whichever one makes the most sense
and looks the cleanest there's no right
or wrong answer there is no magic time
frame there is no nothing it's just the
one that I'm going get this as a poster
yes it's whichever one makes the most
sense and looks the cleanest for my
personal self I like the 30 minute
there's times where it's the one hour
there's times where it's the 15 minute
but it it's really you only got to pick
from three that's that's really it like
there's no there's more there's the five
minute 3 minute 1 minute 30 second all
this crazy [\h__\h] all you got to do is
pick from these three I've shorten it
down to that you just pick whichever one
makes the most sense simple right is
this clear does this make sense just you
guys are notice how easier is because
bro why did I not why did I not think of
this from the beginning man this is
crazy these boxes are like helping a lot
like this is crazy so now what do we do
what do we do now in step four exactly
what it says right here right if we're
waiting for a higher low now we are
after Rec creating a potential higher
low lower high we're in constant
moderating the 15 30 minute 1 hour time
frame so that's exactly what we're going
to go do we're going to go down to the
30 time frame and we're going to monitor
when it's going to go from bearish to
bullish so that's exactly what we're
here for you guys can see as of right
now
whatever we are creating a lower low so
we'll mark this as a lower
high right here and then we will mark
this as a lower
low why is there a Gap I have no idea uh
probably like these replay things just
I'm telling you the replay thing is just
out of whack that's why I don't like
back tesing like I just don't like it um
so here you have
this
oh what do we do now oh Cameron is like
oh [\h__\h] Mandy is like oh the time is
here all right so what do we have the
strategy it's here so now comes the
final step the moment we have all been
waiting for final step which is
five final step five yeah right
okay
so once we get the shift of
structure
on 15 minute 30 minute
hour looks
cleaner We Now look for an
engulfing what the hell man my SP look
for engulfing
on
the 1 Hour 2 hours
Hour
whichever looks the
cleanest and
cool does this make sense is this simple
so after we get the shift of structure
on the 15 minute 30 minute 1 hour
whichever one looks cleaner We Now look
for an engulfing on the 1 Hour 2 hour or
4 hour so if we noticed we looked for
the shift of structure here and now we
look for the entries here and we're
buying at these time frames it's very
simple we guys are seen how each time
frame has a purpose and how we go back
and forth I
swear yeah literally if I ever do
another boot camp like this is just like
this is it like this is literally it so
after we now do the shift of structure
then we have we're going to look for an
engulfing on the 1 Hour 2 Hour 4 Hour
wherever it looks cleaner obviously the
strongest confirmation the higher the
time frame the stronger the confirmation
simple you guys have any questions type
one if you get if if we I'll
get can you put the steps right next to
each other so we so I take a picture
yeah I got you no worries like at the
end I'm going to do everything you'll
see and I'm going to make this dope I'm
going to make like I'm going to make
this better for like the future right so
as of right now we have the shifted
structure so now we go to whatever it
says right here this is literally the
strateg so we just going to follow this
now this says go to the 1 Hour 2 Hour 4
Hour whichever looks cleaner okay bet
it's exactly what I'm going to do as you
can tell here technically obviously this
is why I hate the back testing because
this that's not where it is you notice
price is down here it's not up there or
whatever right so technically we would
have an engulfing here on the 1
hour um then we would
have a bullish pin bar on the 2hour and
then the 4 Hour we would have a 4 Hour
pin bar so exactly what I just said we
type up so right here waiting for higher
low so this is where we go to number
four and we
go 30
minute shift of
structure then we go to number seven
which is I hour after the shift of
structure what comes next which is the
final step it is our entry signal so
here we put entry
signal
confirmation after the shift of
structure our entry signal confirmation
is 1 hour bullish golfing oh my God
there's too many buff all right so we
have entry signal
confirmation 1 hour bullish engulfing
2our bullish
doy 4our
doy right again this is just everything
this Market is telling me you guys are
seeing that you guys are seeing how all
of that makes
sense that like type one if it makes
sense type if you guys have any
questions perfect okay okay cool that's
it me just s forget that's literally it
that's just that's the whole entire
strategy like it really does not get any
simpler so now it just comes more of
like tedious work which is like um yeah
exactly all you would bet here is just
2% all of this is just 2% so then this
is where we just come to tedious where
not not tedious okay okay we're going to
add another step add another step we're
getting better at
this side note
so this is a side note side notes for
stop loss SL take profit
Place stop
loss at a
point where
is
it stop plusus has to be
placed at okay let me see let me see how
I explain this stoploss has to be
placed
H completely
wrong or
also
at at the shift of structure
15 m
m 1
hour with a five
five to seven pit breathing room all
right does this make sense this is a
side note for the stop loss so when it
comes to placing a stoploss the stop
loss has to be placed at a point where
if hit we are completely wrong also
at the bottom or at the top at the shift
of structure so for this example right
here we're going to go down to the 30
time frame the 30 minute time frame
that's when we had the shift of
structure so if we were to take this
trade right here and then this were to
be our trade this were to be the bottom
of the move 50 whatever you add five
Pips that is the bottom of the shift of
structure meaning if price hits this
point we have now a body closed under
where it's going to potentially create
now a low or low does this make sense
for the stop loss we give it a five or 7
Minute breathing room and then this is
done on the 15 30 minute whenever we get
the shift of structure does this make
sense very self-explanatory type one if
it makes
sense this is crazy fire yeah I'm
telling you this is even fire for myself
because I feel like now I'm just going
to save so much time on explaining
things for you guys like it's fire could
have made yeah yeah okay perfect so now
this is
where we come again for the side note
side note for stoploss placement so
let's just
do this is going to be its own side note
stoploss for side and then we're going
to have stop um side
notes for take
profit placement
sign
know okay sign note for take profit
placement buying at Daily higher
low if buying at we start from the top
buying at
weekly area of interest and aiming
for weekly higher low
is placed
at let me see how I explain this in a
second if buying at weekly air of
interest and aiming for a weekly higher
low so what do I mean by that if leveled
the [\h__\h] up so if we are buying at a
weekly area of Interest this is weekly
area of interest and we are aiming for a
weekly higher
high aiming for a weekly higher
high stop loss
is to be placed
at take profit one is to be placed at
previous higher hat so if you are buying
here if you are buying here on the
weekly this is your stop loss your take
profit one is at the previous higher
high does that make sense is that
simple you guys have any questions on
this is this how it should be explained
or takeprofit one is to be placed at
higher high I don't think it's previous
higher high it's just at higher high
structure
Point bodies
so again this is telling you right here
if buying at weekly area of Interest
your take profit is at the weekly this
is a sment and again same thing for
here if
buying at a
daily area of interest and aiming for
a
daily higher high take profit is to be
at the structure Point does that